[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress appeared in the 1999 drama movie Magnolia, also starring Tom Cruise?", "correct_answer": "Julianne Moore", "incorrect_answers": ["Reese Witherspoon", "Julia Roberts", "Minnie Driver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrays plastic surgeon Dr. Einstein in Arsenic and Old Lace?", "correct_answer": "Peter Lorre", "incorrect_answers": ["John Alexander", "Raymond Massey", "Cary Grant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was Scarlett Johansson born?", "correct_answer": "In the USA", "incorrect_answers": ["In Germany", "In Canada", "In Denmark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When a hydrogen atom loses its electron it might form which of the following?", "correct_answer": "A proton", "incorrect_answers": ["A neutron", "A lepton", "A quark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Tibetan name of Mt. Everest?", "correct_answer": "Chomolungma", "incorrect_answers": ["Appa Sherpa", "Sagarmatha", "Temba Tsheri"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jupiter, the fifth planet from the Sun, has atmosphere composed of what gases?", "correct_answer": "Hydrogen and helium", "incorrect_answers": ["Oxygen and hydrogen", "Hydrogen and nitrogen", "Oxygen and nitrogen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Octopuses can live in fresh water.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The pork pie hat is associated with the representatives of this popular music genre.", "correct_answer": "Jazz", "incorrect_answers": ["Metal", "Rock", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tiger shark reaches a length of 10 ft to 20 ft.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which jazz musician sang  Weve Got  All The Time In The World, in On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Louis Armstrong", "incorrect_answers": ["Nat King Cole", "Perry Como", "Smokey Robinson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Moe Berg was a professional baseball player, a catcher. Which one of these statements about him is correct?", "correct_answer": "He was an international spy.", "incorrect_answers": ["He  was the only catcher to catch three no hitters.", "He was the last out in Don Larsens perfect game.", "He was on base when Ruth hit home run number 60."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the path taken by a bullet fired from a rifle into the air (ignoring friction)?", "correct_answer": "A parabola", "incorrect_answers": ["A straight line", "A logarithmic line", "An exponential line"]}]